<properties>
	<property id="00" note="Entire record parsed and ingested without errors, record may have a Product record in the Acknowledgement which itself may have a &lt;RecordStatusNote&gt; or &lt;RecordStatusDetail&gt; to convey information, editorial queries or warnings"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[No record errors]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="01" note="Entire record parsed and ingested without errors, record MUST have a Product record in the Acknowledgement with a &lt;RecordStatusNote&gt; or at least one &lt;RecordStatusDetail&gt; to convey errors in associated media files (and possibly supplementary editorial queries)"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[No record errors – errors in collateral]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="02" note="Record parsed and ingested with errors, record MUST have a Product record in the Acknowledgement with a &lt;RecordStatusNote&gt; or at least one &lt;RecordStatusDetail&gt; to convey errors (and possibly supplementary information, editorial queries or warnings). At least SOME of the data in the original Product record has been ingested. There may also be errors in associated media files"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Record with errors]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="03" note="Entire record rejected, record MUST have a Product record in the Acknowedgemet, with a &lt;RecordStatusNote&gt; or at least one &lt;RecordStatusDetail&gt; to convey errors (and possibly supplementary information, editorial queries or warnings). NONE of the data in the original Product record has been ingested"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Record rejected]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="09" note="Record status reported in an earlier Acknowledgement message, based on partial processing of ONIX message. The record MUST NOT have a Product record in this Acknowledgement. Code not valid in &lt;RecordStatusDetail&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Reported previously]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
</properties>