<properties>
	<property id="01" note="Resource Version Feature Value carries a code from List 178"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[File format]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="02" note="Resource Version Feature Value carries an integer"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Image height in pixels]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="03" note="Resource Version Feature Value carries an integer"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Image width in pixels]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="04" note="Resource Version Feature Value carries the filename of the supporting resource, necessary only when it is different from the last part of the path provided in &lt;ResourceLink&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Filename]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="05" note="Resource Version Feature Value carries a decimal number only, suggested no more than 2 or 3 significant digits (eg 1.7, not 1.7462 or 1.75MB)"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Approximate download file size in megabytes]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="06" note="MD5 hash value of the resource file. &lt;ResourceVersionFeatureValue&gt; should contain the 128-bit digest value (as 32 hexadecimal digits). Can be used as a cryptographic check on the integrity of a resource after it has been retrieved"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[MD5 hash value]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="07" note="Resource Version Feature Value carries a integer number only (eg 1831023)"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Exact download file size in bytes]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="08" note="SHA-256 hash value of the resource file. &lt;ResourceVersionFeatureValue&gt; should contain the 256-bit digest value (as 64 hexadecimal digits). Can be used as a cryptographic check on the integrity of a resource after it has been retrieved"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[SHA-256 hash value]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="09" note="International Standard Content Code, a ‘similarity hash’ derived algorithmically from the resource content itself (see https://iscc.codes). &lt;IDValue&gt; is the ISCC-CODE generated from a digital manifestation of the work, as a variable-length case-insensitive alphanumeric string (or 55 characters including three hyphens if using ISCC v1.0, but this is deprecated). Note alphabetic characters in v1.x ISCCs use Base32 encoding and are conventionally upper case. The ‘ISCC:’ prefix is omitted"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[ISCC]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="10" note="&lt;ResourceVersionFeatureValue&gt; carries the previous filename of the supporting resource, necessary only when it is different from the last part of the path provided in &lt;ResourceLink&gt; and from the filename provided using &lt;ResourceVersionFeatureType&gt; code 04, and when the data sender suggests the recipient delete this old file. Note that the ‘trigger’ to update the resource and delete the old file is provided by the Resource version’s &lt;ContentDate&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Previous filename]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
</properties>