<properties>
	<property id="01" note="Credit that must be displayed when a resource is used (eg ‘Photo Jerry Bauer’ or ‘© Magnum Photo’). Credit text should be carried in &lt;FeatureNote&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Required credit]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="02" note="Explanatory caption that may accompany a resource (eg use to identify an author in a photograph). Caption text should be carried in &lt;FeatureNote&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Caption]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="03" note="Copyright holder of resource (indicative only, as the resource can be used without consultation). Copyright text should be carried in &lt;FeatureNote&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Copyright holder]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="04" note="Approximate length in minutes of an audio or video resource. &lt;FeatureValue&gt; should contain the length of time as an integer number of minutes"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Length in minutes]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="05" note="Use to link resource such as a contributor image to a contributor unambiguously. Use for example with Resource Content types 04, 11–14 from List 158, particularly where the product has more than a single contributor. &lt;FeatureValue&gt; contains the 16-digit ISNI, which must match an ISNI given in an instance of &lt;Contributor&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[ISNI of resource contributor]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="06" note="Use to link resource such as a contributor image to a contributor unambiguously. Use for example with Resource Content types 04, 11–14 from List 158, particularly where the product has more than a single contributor. &lt;FeatureValue&gt; contains the proprietary ID, which must match a proprietary ID given in an instance of &lt;Contributor&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Proprietary ID of resource contributor]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="07" note="&lt;FeatureNote&gt; is Alternative text for the resource, which might be presented to visually-impaired readers"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Resource alternative text]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="08" note="&lt;FeatureValue&gt; is a 24-bit RGB or 32-bit RBGA color in hexadecimal, eg fff2de for an opaque warm cream. Used when the resource – for example a 3D image of the product – includes a background, or if used with an alpha channel, when the image is irregularly shaped or contains a semi-transparent shadow thrown against a background"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Background color of image resource]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="09" note="&lt;FeatureValue&gt; is an ONIX code from List 256 that describes an attribute of a product image resource (eg perspective of 3D view, content)"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Attribute of product image resource]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="10" note="&lt;FeatureValue&gt; is a 24-bit RGB color in hexadecimal, eg ffc300 for a rich yellow-orange, used when the resource supplier requests a specific background color be displayed behind the resource on a web page"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Background color of page]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="11" note="Use to link resource such as a contributor image to a contributor unambiguously, for example with Resource Content types 04, 11–14 from List 158, particularly where the product has more than a single contributor. &lt;FeatureValue&gt; contains the 16-digit ORCID, which must match an ORCID given in an instance of &lt;Contributor&gt;"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[ORCID of resource contributor]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
</properties>