<properties>
	<property id="01" note="Product A is or includes a manifestation of work X. (There is a direct parent–child relation between work X and the product). The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work X"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Manifestation of]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="02" note="Product A is or includes a manifestation of a work X which is derived (directly) from related work W in one or more of the ways specified in the former ISTC rules. (There is a relationship between a grandparent work W and a parent work X, and between that parent work and the product.) This relation type is intended to enable products with a common ‘grandparent’ work to be linked without specifying the precise nature of their derivation, and without necessarily assigning an identifier to the product’s parent work X. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work W. Codes 20–30 may be used instead to provide details of the derivation of work X from work W"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="03" note="Product A is a manifestation of a work X from which related work Y is (directly) derived in one or more of the ways specified in the former ISTC rules. (There is a relationship between a parent work X and a child work Y, and between the parent work X and the product.) The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work Y. Codes 40–50 may be used instead to provide details of the derivation of work Y from work X"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="04" note="Product A is a manifestation of a work X in the same (bibliographic) collection as related work Z. (There is a relationship between the parent work X and a ‘same collection’ work Z, and between the parent work X and the product.) The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work Z"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Other work in same (bibliographic) collection]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="05" note="Product A is a manifestation of a work X by the same contributor(s) as related work Z. (There is a relationship between the parent work X and a work Z where X and Z have at least one contributor in common, and between the parent work X and the product.) The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work Z"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Other work by same contributor]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="06" note="Product A is or includes a manifestation of work X. (There is a direct parent–child relation between work X and the product, and work X is original, ie not a derived work of any kind – there is no work W.) The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work X. See code 01 if the originality of X is unspecified or unknown"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Manifestation of original work]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="21" note="Product A is or includes a manifestation of a work X which is derived directly from related work W by abridgement. (There is a relationship between the grandparent [unabridged] work W and the parent [abridged] work X, and between the parent work X and the product.) The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [unabridged] work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of product A would normally be ABR. See code 02 if the method of derivation of X from W is unknown or unstated. The [abridged] parent work X may be identified using a separate instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; with relation code 01"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by abridgement]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="22" note="Product A is or includes a manifestation of a work X which is derived directly from related work W by annotation. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [unannotated] work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of product X would normally be ANN, VAR etc. See code 02 if the method of derivation of X from W is unknown or unstated. The [annotated] parent work X may be identified using a separate instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; with relation code 01"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by annotation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="23" note="The content of the work X has been formed by compilation of work W and another work Z. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of product A may be CMB. Work Z may be identified using a separate instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; with code 23. The compiled parent work X may be identified using a separate instance of &lt;Related&gt; work with relation code 01"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by compilation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="24" note="The content of the work W has been augmented by the addition of critical commendary to form work X. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of Product A would normally be CRI"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by criticism]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="25" note="The content of the work X is an excerpt from work W. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [complete] work W"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by excerption]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="26" note="Offensive or unsuitable text material has been removed from work W to form work X. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [unsuitable] work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of Product A would normally be EXP"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by expurgation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="27" note="The content of work W has been augmented by the addition of significant non-textual elements to form work X. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [unaugmented] work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of product A may be ILL, ENH etc"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by addition (of non-text material)]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="28" note="The content of work W has been revised and/or expanded or enlarged to form work X [including addition, deletion or replacement of text material]. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [unrevised] work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of product A may be REV, NED, etc, or A may be numbered"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by revision]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="29" note="The content of work W has been translated into another language to form work X. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [untranslated] work W"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from via translation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="30" note="The content of work W has been adapted [into a different literary form] to form work X. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for [unadapted] work W. &lt;EditionType&gt; of product A would normally be ADP, ACT etc"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from via adaptation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="31" note="The content of work W has been modified by the removal of significant non-textual elements to form work X. The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include an identifier for work W"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from by subtraction (of non-text material)]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="41" note="Product A is a manifestation of a work X from which the related work Y is (directly) derived by abridgement. (There is a relationship between the parent [unabridged] work X and the child [abridged] work Y, and between parent work X and the product.) The instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; must include the identifier for [abridged] work Y. See code 03 if the method of derivation of Y from X is unknown or unstated. The [unabridged] parent work X may be identified using a separate instance of &lt;RelatedWork&gt; with relation code 01 or 06"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by abridgement]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="42" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by annotation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="43" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by compilation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="44" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by criticism]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="45" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by excerption]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="46" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by expurgation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="47" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by addition (of non-text material)]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="48" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this by revision]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="49" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this via translation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="50" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Related work is derived from this via adaptation]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="51" note=""/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Derived from this by subtraction (of non-text material)]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="98" note="Product A is or includes a manifestation of an expression of LRM work X. Do not use, except as a workaround for differences between LRM works and expressions, and ONIX works in LRM library practice, and always also include a relationship to an ONIX work using code 01"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Manifestation of LRM work]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
	<property id="99" note="Product A is or includes a manifestation of an LRM expression with the same content, same agents and in the same modality (text, audio, video etc) as work X. Do not use, except as a workaround for differences between LRM expressions and ONIX works in LRM library practice, and always also include a relationship to an ONIX work using code 01"/>
		<name>
			<language id="en"><![CDATA[Manifestation of LRM expression]]></language>
		</name>
	</property>
</properties>